Guide to the Robert Richardson Sears Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-1986-046
  - Special files and correspondence (Box 8)
    - Flood, Margaret (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence, F-H, 1949-1950 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Gewitz, Jacob L. (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Nowlis, Vincent (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - N-R (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - S-Z (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Sears, Pauline and Bob (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Sears, Vita (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Sears publications (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Special file - episodic analysis (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - SRCD Governing Council and Archives (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - American Philosophical Society (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Annual Review of Psychology (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Bing nursery school file - personal (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Broom Closet Society (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Boys Town center (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Geriatic Research Center (Dr. Franklin C. Ebaugh) (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Harvard alumni speech (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - International Psychological Association (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Mark Twain's exhibitionisms (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - National Science Foundation (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Patterns: royalty problems (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Perceptual and motor skills (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Permissions (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Reviews by R. R. Sears (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Sex conference report (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Society of Experimental Psychologists (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Social Science Research Council (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Stanford Press and Libraries (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - TRANS Action Publications (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Your ancients revisited (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence circa 1978-1981 (Box 9)
    - Correspondence, A (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, B (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, C (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, D (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, E (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, F (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, G (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, H (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, I (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, J (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence, K (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence, L (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, M (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence, N (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence, O (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence, P (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence, Q (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence, R (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence, S (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence, T (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence, U (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence, V (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence, W (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence, X (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Correspondence, Y (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Correspondence, Z (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Recommendations, Professionals A-L (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Recommendations, Undergraduates A-L (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Recommendations, Professionals M-Z (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Recommendations, Undergraduates M-Z (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Barber, Ann (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Boelkins, Chuck (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Bonvillian, John (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Dillon, Jim - Vita (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Dykstra, Vergil (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Fernandez, Luis (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Ferguson, Lucy Rau (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Greene, Nicki (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Gunnar, Megan (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Heras, Ivonne (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Hoffman, Sue (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - King, Donald (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Litven, Joe - personal file (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Kent, Martha (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Meyer, Lissa (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Moon, Michael (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Olkin, Ingram (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Smith, Willie (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Spelke, Elizabeth (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - Stanton, Ann (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - Strohner, Hans (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - Uyeki, Eugene S. (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - Weinberger, Gerald (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - Zussman, John (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Correspondence from Sept. 1973 through May 1974, 1973 September - 1974 May (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence from Sept. 1973 through May 1974, 1973 September - 1974 May (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Dr. Sears to be filed (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Dr. Sears to be filed (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Depression, Aggression and Punishment (Identity? Study) Conflict? (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Toilet, sex and doll play. Conflict drive. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Newton methods data (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - 101 scatters - SI crossbreaks (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Maccoby - Whiting - deviation stories (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Newton data (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - newton doll play (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Doll play methods chapter - data (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Doll play rehabilitation - Newton data (protocol, calculation, etc.) (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Griffith, Donald - doll play - neurotic child (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Doll play - notes and abstracts (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Pintler doll play - summary sheets, group 1 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Pintler doll play - ditto sheets, group 1 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Yarrow doll play - summary sheets, group 2 (y1, y2, y3) (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Yarrow doll play - ditto sheets, group 2 (y1, y2, y3) (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - KC doll play - ditto sheets (incomplete), group 3 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Hollenberg data - aggression, group data (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Hollenberg data - group responses, group tabulation sheets (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - 1948 doll play - ditto sheets: boys, group 5 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - 1948 doll play - ditto sheets: girls, group 5 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - 1948 doll play protocols: boys, group 5 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - 1949 doll play - ditto sheets: boys, group 6 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - 1949 doll play - ditto sheets: girls, group 6 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Sperry doll play data - ditto sheets, groups 7, 8 and 9 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Sperry doll play data - summary sheets (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Tama doll play - ditto sheets, group 4 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Tama doll play - summary sheets, group 4 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Tama doll play protocols: girls, group 4 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Tama doll play protocols: boys, group 4 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Tama doll play protocols: girls, extra copy (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Tama doll play protocols: boys, extra copy (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Pintler doll play protocols: girls, by ages (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Code numbers for parents (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Code 1 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Code 2 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Code 3 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Code 4 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Code 5 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Code 6 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Code 7 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Code 8 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Code 9 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Code 10 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Code 11 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Code 12 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Code 13 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Code 14 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Code 15 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Code 16 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Code 17 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Code 18 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Code 19 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Code 20 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Code 21 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Code 22 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Code 23 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Code 24 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Code 25 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Code 26 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Code 27 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Code 28 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Code 29 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Code 30 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Code 31 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Code 32 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Code 33 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Code 34 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Code 35 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Code 36 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Code 37 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Code 38 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Code 39 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Code 40 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Code 41 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Code 42 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Code 43 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Code 44 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Code 45 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Aggression statistics: children (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Theory: doll play study (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Pintler raw data (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence on Pintler manuscripts (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Aggression study: father absence paper (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Pintler data: calculation sheets, age differences (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Pintler data: stimulus generalization (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Pintler data: education levels (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Pintler data: content analysis (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Original records: doll play (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Original records: doll play (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Original records: doll play (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Aggression sessions: children (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Pintler protocols (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Pintler normative tables (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Pintler data: session to session material, latency of aggression (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Pintler data: statistical treatment (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Pintler data: two sessions by agent (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - Completed Pintler manuscripts carbons (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Graphs for Pintler paper (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Copies of Pintler tables and figures (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Pintler data: calculation sheets, sex differences (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Aggression study: sibling data (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - "Factor" intercorrelations: Antec. (M,F.) (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - Agent-Object tabulations: Identif. Perm. Doll Play: Session 1, 1958 (Box 11B, Folder 1)
  - Agent-Object tabulations: Identif. Perm. Doll Play: Session 1 (Box 11B, Folder 2)
  - Files of older studies, 1932-1947 (Box 12)
    - Fluid research fund, 1936-1937 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - A hypothesis concerning cortical localization of inhibitory processes comprising hysterical anesthesia (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Decortication (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Public lectures (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Projection of sissiness with respect to pride (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Adrenalin: artificial induction of emotion (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Conditional abdominal reflex (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Attentional learning (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Aphesia: Ghardino, "Cerebal Localization," Proceeding Assn. Res. Nev. and Mental Disorder, 1934 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Autobiography notes and J. G. Corr. statistics (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Conflict: measurement (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Psychology of conflict theory (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Regression (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Selection perception (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Projection (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Abnormalities of memory (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Displacement (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Abnormal (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Conditional response (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - C. R. in fish (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Hypnosis (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Fish: experimental group (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Protocols: completed fish (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Fish: normal control (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Fish: total ablation (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Blind fish: nos. 1 and 2 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Preliminary work: ring technique (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Goldfish maze (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Hysterical astereognosis: Arch. Neur. and Psychiat., 1933 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Hysterical anesthesia: Arch. Neur. and Psychiat., 1933 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Luminal intoxication: Bessner (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Projection: experiment 1 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Projection: ideas of reference (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Ideas of reference: data (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Nipple withdrawal: data (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - K. Cobb dependency data (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - K. Cobb dependency data (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Kansas City studies: basic K.C. doll house play, tabulations (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - K.C. studies: tabulations, etc. (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - K.C. studies: K.C. interview scales and tabulations (ortho. paper) (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - K.C. studies: cup feeding experiments (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - K.C. studies: K.C. nursery, raw data and statistics (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - K.C. studies: articulation (cup feeding) (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - K.C. studies: Kansas City sucking project (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - K.C. studies: K.C. doll play, checklist raw data (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Virshup data: Magranahan repression (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Virshup original tests: Magranahan repression (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Correspondence: Yale, 1936-1937 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Notes on repression (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Sears on frustration and aggression (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Frustration: aggression system (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - Chapter 1: Frustration-Aggression system (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Postulate systems (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Aggression (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Aggression and anxiety (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Regression (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Substitute behavior: book (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Development of values (property, etc.) (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Dissertation papers, theses, and theory memos (Box 13)
    - Outlines for books by RSS (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Identification memo-notes and preliminary stuff for Cambridge study (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Pictures (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - L of a paper presented at meetings (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Lubrecht, Charles private patient care, 1942 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Dollard, criteria for the Life History 1935 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - R. S. Angier History (Yale), 1929 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Warren - history of Assoc. Psychology (outline) (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Mental Hygiene Instit. (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Psychology 30 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Prof. seminar notes (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Personality as action (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - AST Course SVI, 1943-1944 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Child welfare 233 - psychology of personality (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Dynamic psychology I: Freud (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Dynamic psychology II (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Seminar in personality (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Sweet personal attitude test (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Implications of intelligence and intelligence testing for mental hygiene (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Brief illustrative case studies (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Clinical aids (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Sex education and bibliographies for patients (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Occupational choices and interests (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Brodbeck's graphs (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Dependency and independence in young children by (Manu) Beller (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Beller thesis (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Social science and social relations commencement address, 1949 February (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Presidential address (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Blane, Howard T. thesis (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - A study of the food habits of children on an institutional diet by Frances G. Adlis, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Merrill thesis (M.A.) (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Merrill Ph.D. thesis (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Anna Freud seminars and reprints, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - A study of the role of personality and environmental factors in obesity by Dorthy J. Gill (thesis (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Thesis - Phillips, Ruth (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Thesis - Pintler, Peg (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Thesis - Jones, Laurel (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - The expression of guilt in fantasy and reality by K. R. Wurtz, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Gillete article on doll furniture (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Robinson (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Dean, Daphne thesis (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Personality development in contemporary culture (unused parts) by RSS (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Thompson, Jean - feeding thesis (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Thesis publications (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Identification (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Cultural components in responses to pain by Mark Zborowski (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Consequences of permissiveness for parents of young children by Robin O. Blood Jr. (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Thompson, Clare Wright paper, 1953 July 23 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Infant feeding abstracts also sucking (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Oral activity, erotism, etc. (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - GWWW - cross-cultural stuff (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Heathers - dependency (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Effects of socialization methods (severity, etc.) - general personality development - book on (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - Personality development - book on (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Doll play book (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - Sex - typing (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - Sex theory (Box 13, Folder 57)
    - Infantile sexuality (Box 13, Folder 58)
    - Projector (Box 13, Folder 59)
    - Displacement (Box 13, Folder 60)
    - Maturation (Gesell, etc.) (Box 13, Folder 61)
    - Fantasy (imaginary playmates, etc.) (Box 13, Folder 62)
    - Competition theory (Seminar Spring), 1948 (Box 13, Folder 63)
    - Anal erotism (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Northrops seminar (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Catharsis and aggression (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Annoyances deductions (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Art and communications (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Terman article (drawings and protocol) - Reaction of subjects to experiment and experimenter (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Repression and amnesia - Sharp and Flanagan Theses (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Projective play (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Tom Sawyer (Ross Dixon) (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Educational psychology and measurement 1 - registration list (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Effect of cup, bottle and breast feeding on oral activities of newborn infants (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Relation of cup-feeding in infancy to thumbsucking and the oral drive (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Summary of Barbara Chartier's "Weaverton: A Study of Culture and Personalities in a Southern Mill Town" (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Speech notes: school and home (Lynn, Mass.) (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Clark University speech (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Ingroup (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Case examples (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Memory apparatus calibrations (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Experimental program (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Invitation to aggression (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Conflict - age study (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Abstracts of frustration experiments (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Panic in air raids (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Thematic apperceptions (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - DEMBO technique (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Story completion test (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Status and role (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - General university matters (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Buhler world test (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Rorschach tests (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Anxiety indices (Murphy) (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Student's t-tables (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Character education inquiry (CEI) check list (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Haggerty-Olson-Wickman (H.O.W.) behavior rating (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Laird - personal inventory (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - CEI "How Do You Feel About It?" (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - George Washington University series social intelligence test (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Attitudes and SA test (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Good citizenship test (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Rogers' personality adjustment test (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - The Ruggles distraction test (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Child behavior (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Monday night, 1941; Bakke; Mowrer (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Monday night meeting - report on Frustration and Aggression (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Hull's seminar (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Hull's seminar (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Abstract of S-R sessions of Monday-Night Group, 1938-1939 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Papers presented before the Monday Night Group, 1939-1944 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Seminar reports - Hull, 1936-1940 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Ad hoc committee - ethical standards (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Visiting committee of the Harvard Board of Overseers (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Modern thought and literature committee (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Search committee for new Dean: School of Education, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence - R. R. Sears (Dean), 1969 August - 1970 April (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Washington trip - Board of Trustees (CASBS), 1972 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Wolman, Benjamin - dictionary definitions (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Society of experimental psychologies (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Analysis schedule: identification code book, copy 1 (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - Analysis schedule: identification code book, copy 2 (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Self-concept scales (Box 14, 14, Folder 60, 60)
  - Survey of attitudes towards children's behavior (key) (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - MCI tables (Identification project) (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - Center for advanced study in the behavioral sciences, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Overseers committee - CASBS (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - SRCD, first report (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - NY conference, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Personality - objective exams (Illinois) (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Personality objective exames (Yale), 1938-1939, 1939-1940 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Clinical psychology exams (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Psychology 12 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Psychology 24 - abnormal (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Psychology 26a (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Personality seminar (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Abnormal notes and material (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Abnormal objective exams (Illinois) (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Undergraduate teaching (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Psychology 12 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Syllabi (Yale) (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Educational psychology notes (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - General experimental psychology exams (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Paranoid exhibits - abnormal psychology (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Abnormal exams (Yale) (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Psychology 1, 1956-1958 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Psychology 1, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Psychology 211 - advanced child psychology, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Psychology 211, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Reading list - child psychology (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Hawaii, summer class, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Psychology 110, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Psychology 110, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Social relations (Harvard) - development of the child. Notebook, course notes. Repression; dominance; distraction; problemsl aggression, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Festinger - % of agreement (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Mimeo seminar reports (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Cross-cultural ratings on socialization practices - Whiting (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Desirable properties of a basic social science theory, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - War evacuation problems (children) (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Statists syllabus (Hull), 1929-1930 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Tests (Illinois) 1932-1936; Yale 1936-1942, 1932-1936, 1936-1942 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Competition and status bibliography (seminar), 1947 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Elimination interview (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Discipline - system analysis (Phillips) (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Aggression test (Duob and Sears) (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Sweet's personal attitudes (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Watson - fair mindedness (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Woodworth/Cody/Matthews (test) (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Joke test (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Terman - Miles M. F. test (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Pressey X-O (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Bernreuter and M-F test scores (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Bernreuter - personality inventory (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Correlations (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Detective stories (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Church attendance (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Suicide (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Economic indices (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Jacobson test scoring key (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Maslow test (woman dominance) (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Bridgman, James (Rohscharch) (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Kenneday, James D. (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - MacDonald (aphasia) (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Hepburn (aphasia) (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Variability - success and failure (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Bach interview schedule (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Gewirtz (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Brodbeck (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - CWRS research programs, 1942-1943 (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Attitudes - notes (Box 15, Folder 64)